[
  {
    "id": "question-Tx102BN4XR7VYHL",
    "question": "Will this phone work with Mint mobile",
    "votes": 0,
    "date": "2022/05/17",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx2FFMR9U80827N",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx102BN4XR7VYHL/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "No, not if it is the LTE version.",
        "badge_text": "",
        "is_manufacturer": false,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/09/08",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 1
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09MZCQGS5",
    "product_name": "SAMSUNG Galaxy A03s Cell Phone, Factory Unlocked Android Smartphone, 32GB, Triple Lens Camera, Infinity Display Screen, Long Battery Life, Expandable Storage, US Version, Blue",
    "product_ratings_count": 605
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx2ZUEKVIR9CNOK",
    "question": "Headphone jack????",
    "votes": 2,
    "date": "2022/08/13",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx1LON36L6Z6FPJ",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx2ZUEKVIR9CNOK/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Hi Cindy. Yes, the phone has a headphone jack. ^Christian",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/08/13",
        "upvotes": 2,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09XFJY4N4",
    "product_name": "TracFone Blu View 2 (2022) 4G LTE Prepaid Smartphone (Locked) - Black - 32GB - Sim Card Included - CDMA",
    "product_ratings_count": 158
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx12IOL3SV2WCG4",
    "question": "What headphones work with this phone?",
    "votes": 1,
    "date": "2022/04/10",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx1FREWH0HYBLGR",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx12IOL3SV2WCG4/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Dear Valued Customer. Please know that this phone is compatible with 3.5mm headphone jack. ^Marvin",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/04/10",
        "upvotes": 2,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09NWDJQ78",
    "product_name": "Tracfone Motorola moto g Pure (2021), 32GB, Blue - Prepaid Smartphone (Locked)",
    "product_ratings_count": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx37N97WJE6A919",
    "question": "Is this device Dual Sim i.e. 2 physical sim slots?",
    "votes": 2,
    "date": "2022/03/11",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx2UELYYLP0GT30",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx37N97WJE6A919/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Mine only is only capable of one SIM card.",
        "badge_text": "",
        "is_manufacturer": false,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/03/11",
        "upvotes": 2,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09MVZSW5V",
    "product_name": "SAMSUNG Galaxy S22 Ultra Cell Phone, Factory Unlocked Android Smartphone, 128GB, 8K Camera & Video, Brightest Display Screen, S Pen, Long Battery Life, Fast 4nm Processor, US Version, Phantom Black",
    "product_ratings_count": 603
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx124JJBVHIP58J",
    "question": "Expandable storage?",
    "votes": 21,
    "date": "2021/01/17",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx1VWF4X83897HF",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx124JJBVHIP58J/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Thanks for your interest. Yes, the Motorola One 5G Ace supports expandable storage (microSD card up to 1TB.) - Mike",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2021/01/28",
        "upvotes": 138,
        "downvotes": 3
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B08NWD7K8H",
    "product_name": "Motorola One 5G Ace | 2021 | 2-Day battery | Unlocked | Made for US by Motorola | 6/128GB | 48MP Camera | Hazy Silver",
    "product_ratings_count": 3
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx102BN4XR7VYHL",
    "question": "Will this phone work with Mint mobile",
    "votes": 0,
    "date": "2022/05/17",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx2FFMR9U80827N",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx102BN4XR7VYHL/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "No, not if it is the LTE version.",
        "badge_text": "",
        "is_manufacturer": false,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/09/08",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 1
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09MZBTMQQ",
    "product_name": "SAMSUNG Galaxy A03s Cell Phone, Factory Unlocked Android Smartphone, 32GB, 3 Camera Lenses, Infinity Display Screen, Long Battery Life, Expandable Storage, US Version, Black",
    "product_ratings_count": 605
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx10RR4904DGRW2",
    "question": "I'm having difficulty finding the proper phone case and screen protector for this model. What key words do i need to type to attain proper protection?",
    "votes": 6,
    "date": "2021/06/29",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx1KVJKPTDHZH1I",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx10RR4904DGRW2/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Search Amazon for: \"Case Moto G stylus 2021\" (2020 model will NOT fit)",
        "badge_text": "",
        "is_manufacturer": false,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2021/11/16",
        "upvotes": 4,
        "downvotes": 1
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B092BYTXM3",
    "product_name": "Moto G Stylus 5G | 2021 | 2-Day battery | Unlocked | Made for US by Motorola | 6/256GB | 48MP Camera | Cosmic Emerald",
    "product_ratings_count": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx2YU9TTQGKHMYG",
    "question": "can Q link(US) sim work in this phone?",
    "votes": 1,
    "date": "2022/07/25",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx3MWTKPODVIDPM",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx2YU9TTQGKHMYG/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Yes, I am using Qlink SIM on it.",
        "badge_text": "",
        "is_manufacturer": false,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/08/10",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B0B14LBNL6",
    "product_name": "OnePlus Nord N20 5G |Android Smart Phone |6.43\" AMOLED Display|6+128GB |U.S. Unlocked |4500 mAh Battery | 33W Fast Charging | Blue Smoke",
    "product_ratings_count": 128
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx246D5UTD6THFB",
    "question": "does this phone display minutes and days remaining on the face page?",
    "votes": 3,
    "date": "2022/02/14",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx1V1G8AU15CG6W",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx246D5UTD6THFB/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Hi Maggie. Unfortunately, the remaining balance (talk, text, data and service days) will not display on the phone\u2019s screen. In order to check the balance, you will need to text the keyword \u201cBALANCE\u201d or numerical code \u201c411\u201d to short code 611611. ^Marvin",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/02/14",
        "upvotes": 3,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09CLN4LLN",
    "product_name": "Tracfone Alcatel TCL A3, 32GB, Black - Prepaid Smartphone (Locked)",
    "product_ratings_count": 752
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx11GMP2DA7XERV",
    "question": "Does this work with wifi on T-Mobile sim?",
    "votes": 0,
    "date": "2022/03/08",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx321SX1W3FXTY",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx11GMP2DA7XERV/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "No",
        "badge_text": "",
        "is_manufacturer": false,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/03/08",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09CBSS3BX",
    "product_name": "Nokia C01 Plus | Android 11 (Go Edition) | Unlocked Smartphone | 2-Day Battery | 2/32GB | 6.52-Inch Screen | Dark Blue",
    "product_ratings_count": 369
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx11FN1ZUHS4Y52",
    "question": "Can i transfer myself  or do i need a  tech",
    "votes": 0,
    "date": "2022/03/30",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx3EKBGRKCKZJ22",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx11FN1ZUHS4Y52/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Hi Carolyn. Please be informed that you can transfer your service and phone number from one device to another. You may text the keyword \u201cTransfer\u201d to 611611. ^Kathleen",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/03/30",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09CLMK872",
    "product_name": "Simple Mobile Samsung Galaxy A32 5G, 64GB - Prepaid Smartphone (Locked), Black",
    "product_ratings_count": 19
  },
  {
    "id": "question-TxFAWQQPP1ZM8R",
    "question": "What is the charger type?",
    "votes": 0,
    "date": "2022/07/24",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx3OMBIADZKZZE7",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/TxFAWQQPP1ZM8R/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Hi Waseem. The charger of this device is a USB type C. ^Christian",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/07/25",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09X7GCNYY",
    "product_name": "Simple Mobile Nokia C200 4G LTE Prepaid Smartphone (Locked) - 32GB - Black - Sim Card Included - GSM",
    "product_ratings_count": 0
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx1A7Q2SITXPJMJ",
    "question": "I currently live in Panama. If I buy it, does it work?",
    "votes": 12,
    "date": "2021/10/20",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-MxKM49UETLCZCL",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx1A7Q2SITXPJMJ/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Yes it will work; I currently live in Panama, have been a Google phone user since their nexus line and currently own a Pixel 5 (previously had a Pixel 3) that has worked with no problems.\rThe only reason I haven't bought the Pixel 6 is cause my current phone is still in pristine condition, but I do know people who have the Pixel 6 and 6 Pro in Panama and have had no problems whatsoever.",
        "badge_text": "",
        "is_manufacturer": false,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/04/20",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09HJZPFDD",
    "product_name": "Google Pixel 6 \u2013 5G Android Phone - Unlocked Smartphone with Wide and Ultrawide Lens - 128GB - Stormy Black",
    "product_ratings_count": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx10VTP7EJ5ROP1",
    "question": "Does this work on Tmobile?",
    "votes": 6,
    "date": "2022/04/05",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx14V5PFY5E126K",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx10VTP7EJ5ROP1/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Absolutely",
        "badge_text": "",
        "is_manufacturer": false,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/04/29",
        "upvotes": 2,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09R6FJWWS",
    "product_name": "SAMSUNG Galaxy A53 5G A Series Cell Phone, Factory Unlocked Android Smartphone, 128GB, 6.5\u201d FHD Super AMOLED Screen, Long Battery Life, US Version, Black",
    "product_ratings_count": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx17JG52O7U3ATY",
    "question": "what operating system?",
    "votes": 0,
    "date": "2022/06/30",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-MxYMZORRR40RWB",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx17JG52O7U3ATY/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "\u201cHi Les, please be informed that the operating system of the phone in question is Android. ^Loejie\u201d",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/07/01",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09CLMSZ1C",
    "product_name": "Net10 Alcatel TCL A3, 32GB, Black - Prepaid Smartphone (Locked)",
    "product_ratings_count": 94
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx2WVLT5GLL44QT",
    "question": "Does it allow for expandable sd card??",
    "votes": 39,
    "date": "2020/11/03",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-MxBBPKFI9HIL67",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx2WVLT5GLL44QT/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "I just got my Samsung Galaxy S20 FE 5G and I can confirm without a doubt that there IS a slot for a microSD card! The people thumbing down that response are not paying attention. When you pull out the sim tray, there is a \"platform\" on the top labeled \"sim card 1\". You place your sim on that tray. UNDERNEATH is ANOTHER\u2026\n        \n          see more\n        \n\n\n        I just got my Samsung Galaxy S20 FE 5G and I can confirm without a doubt that there IS a slot for a microSD card! The people thumbing down that response are not paying attention. When you pull out the sim tray, there is a \"platform\" on the top labeled \"sim card 1\". You place your sim on that tray. UNDERNEATH is ANOTHER TRAY! You just turn the tray OVER and the other side says, \"sim card 2/microSD card\". You put another sim or your microSD card on THAT. Make sure you have the right size SD card, and/or you're putting it in correctly, for those complaining that it doesn't fit. You have to position it a certain way. Unfortunately, I'm using my phone to answer, so I can't show you in a video, but I was able to figure it out by myself. There ARE videos on YouTube, so just Google how to input your microSD for this device, if you want. (It should be common sense, especially with Google, and yet so many people never research anything prior to buying something, and then complain that they bought a device because it said it has a microSD card, and it doesn't). I just lined up the notches of the microSD card (the way the card is cut) with the notches of the tray, and voila! Now I'm off to buy a bigger microSD card (because I know I can!) ;) Good luck!\n        \n          see less",
        "badge_text": "",
        "is_manufacturer": false,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/07/17",
        "upvotes": 38,
        "downvotes": 4
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09BFRV59N",
    "product_name": "SAMSUNG Galaxy S21 FE 5G Cell Phone, Factory Unlocked Android Smartphone, 128GB, 120Hz Display Screen, Pro Grade Camera, All Day Intelligent Battery, US Version, White",
    "product_ratings_count": 12
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx13VAL5L3WEYQ5",
    "question": "Is this phone compatible with LTE (VoLTE) technology",
    "votes": 0,
    "date": "2022/06/25",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx4266O3UUPL5T",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx13VAL5L3WEYQ5/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Hi David. We are pleased to inform you that it is a 4G VoLTE compatible handset. ^Monique",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/06/25",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09X7FBN66",
    "product_name": "TracFone TCL 30 Z 4G LTE Prepaid Smartphone (Locked) - 32GB - Black - Sim Card Included - CDMA",
    "product_ratings_count": 13
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx109KY3QRCCT0H",
    "question": "does this phone have tty? it came up in my search for tty cell phones.",
    "votes": 0,
    "date": "2022/06/15",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx2XJV8ANBAAUMD",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx109KY3QRCCT0H/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Hi Jojo. I\u2019m very sorry to inform you we don\u2019t support TTY. What I can suggest is to contact the manufacturer Samsung in regards to the compatibility to\rTTY. ^Christian",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2022/06/15",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B08J5DRB63",
    "product_name": "TracFone LG Reflect LTE Prepaid Smartphone (Locked) - Black - 32GB - Sim Card Included - CDMA",
    "product_ratings_count": 497
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx3E45FCBJR3G9J",
    "question": "Does this phone use a micro usb or a type c usb charger??",
    "votes": 1,
    "date": "2021/12/12",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx16R7R1UNLRN0D",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx3E45FCBJR3G9J/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Hi Amber. Please be advised that this phone's connector type is a Micro USB. ^Jesel",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2021/12/12",
        "upvotes": 0,
        "downvotes": 0
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09CLQBB6X",
    "product_name": "total wireless Alcatel TCL A3, 32GB, Black - Prepaid Smartphone (Locked)",
    "product_ratings_count": 156
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx2DRUYUW54MRFF",
    "question": "what is inside is a sim card or voucer Data for 20 dollar?",
    "votes": 2,
    "date": "2019/06/25",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-Mx2GYXO5E2P4RWQ",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx2DRUYUW54MRFF/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "When you buy the sim you get 20$ as credit. \rIt means first month bull 39$ as used , like 20$ for calls and 19 $ data usage  . And you pay first bill 19$",
        "badge_text": "",
        "is_manufacturer": false,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2019/06/25",
        "upvotes": 3,
        "downvotes": 5
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B07P5GP11P",
    "product_name": "Google Fi SIM Card Kit",
    "product_ratings_count": 3
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx10WRHCY0IDYF",
    "question": "If you are parked at a Truck Stop, will it allow everyone to use it, or is it secure with a password or what?",
    "votes": 0,
    "date": "2018/01/01",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-MxKO3QXU37BXTB",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx10WRHCY0IDYF/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Thank you for your question!\rThis product will not allow other users to use the booster as long as there's no other persons in the vehicle with you. This is a multi-user booster, but depending on the signal strength outside, product setup, and other factors, it's going to be a limited range inside the vehicle. If some\u2026\n        \n          see more\n        \n\n\n        Thank you for your question!\rThis product will not allow other users to use the booster as long as there's no other persons in the vehicle with you. This is a multi-user booster, but depending on the signal strength outside, product setup, and other factors, it's going to be a limited range inside the vehicle. If someone were able to use it, it won't cause you to slow down since it's not the booster that's making the signal, but making the connection outside better. The only limitations are the towers itself that are in the area.\rIf there's any other questions that need to be addressed, please give us a call at 866-294-1660 or contact our online support at: support@wilsonelectronics.com\rThank you!\n        \n          see less",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2018/01/03",
        "upvotes": 5,
        "downvotes": 1
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B08WYQND57",
    "product_name": "weBoost Drive Reach OTR - Cell Phone Signal Booster for Trucks and SUVs | Boosts 5G & 4G LTE for All U.S. Carriers - Verizon, AT&T, T-Mobile & more | Made in the U.S. | FCC Approved (model 477154)",
    "product_ratings_count": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "question-Tx2BH9Y7U5C851R",
    "question": "what are the actual measurements the menasurements here don't match other sites",
    "votes": 1,
    "date": "2021/10/14",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "answer-MxKCS8OLJ74N6Z",
        "url": "https://www.amazon.com/ask/questions/Tx2BH9Y7U5C851R/ref=ask_ql_ql_al_hza",
        "answer": "Hi Chuck. Please refer to the below information:\rDimensions: 164 x 75.8 x 8.9 mm (6.46 x 2.98 x 0.35 in)\rWeight: 205 g (7.23 oz)\r^Anafe",
        "badge_text": "Manufacturer",
        "is_manufacturer": true,
        "is_seller": false,
        "date": "2021/10/15",
        "upvotes": 1,
        "downvotes": 1
      }
    ],
    "product_id": "B09CLNLCL1",
    "product_name": "Tracfone Samsung Galaxy A12, 32GB, Black - Prepaid Smartphone (Locked)",
    "product_ratings_count": 321
  }
]